数多に注ぐ　光に洗われた
I was washed by the downpour of light
何かが欠けて　閉じたこの世界で
Something’s missing in this closed off world
地平に溶ける　水平のかなたを
Someone has certainly been looking beyond the horizon
誰かがきっと　見ていた
that melts at ground level
望んだものが　偽りだとしても
Even if what I wished for is nothing but a lie
時がやがては　真実に変えるなら
If in the end time turns into truth
意味も理由も　本当はあるのでしょう
then meaning and reason would really exist, right?
だけど見向きもしないでしょう
But it’ll be looked right past won’t it?
どこへ　どこかへ　流れ流されて行こう
To some place, to somewhere, the stream shall go and be drained
帰り支度のまま　心細い旅路
as I’m preparing to return home, it’s a lonely journey
誰が　誰もが　手を振っては夢のあと
Afterwards, after this dream, everyone will wave their hands
今を確かめるように
as if checking to make sure that they’re awake
人は楽園と呼ぶ　いつか辿り着く場所は
The place I’ll someday arrive at, that place people call paradise
なぜか懐かしい空で
for some reason is in the nostalgic sky
儚げに　おぼろげに　どうしてそんな不安そうに
Fleetingly and vaguely, why so seeming anxiously
覗き込む蓮華鏡
do I peer into the lotus mirror?
色の次には　音までなくなって
The spectrum between colour and sound dies out
寂しさだけが　支配する世界で
In a world controlled by loneliness alone
明けに照らされ
I was shined upon by the dawn
それでも濁り酒は　月を映した
but even so my cloudy sake reflected the moon
近く楽園はもう　永遠じゃないと知り
Knowing that the close by paradise is no longer eternal
静かに役を終える
and quietly ending your duty
たとえその日が来ても
for example even if that day did come
あなたはあなたのままで　在り続けるのでしょう
you would continue to remain the same as you are wouldn’t you?
故に、永遠の巫女
And so, would be an eternal shrine maiden
楽園はまた　生まれ変わろうとしてる
Paradise tries to be reborn again
とても懐かしい空へ
towards a very nostalgic sky
陰と陽、夢想、綺想が
Yin and yang, dreams, and fantastic ideas
終わるじゃなく繋がる
are connected without an end
此処が夢、此処が境
Here is a dream, here is a border
楽園はただ　全てを受け入れよう
Paradise shall just accept everything
忘れ去られた　全て
everything that was forgotten
それは東の国の　名前のない御伽噺
That’s the nursery rhyme without a name from that eastern country
遙か遠きに　失はれた幻想
Far away off in the distance, the fantasies that were lost
続いてく
continue on